Pamela Heystek

Mobile: 0410 1969 76 Email: pamela.e.heystek@gmail.com Portfolio: https://peglione.github.io/Portfolio/

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/pamela-heystek/ **GitHub:** https://github.com/PegliOne

Professional Summary

I'm a smart, hard-working Junior Software Engineer who completed General Assembly's Software Engineering Immersive course and then worked for Livewire Markets. I am passionate about building a career in tech, Because I enjoy building user-friendly applications, solving problems and learning new skills. I always strive to write neat efficient and readable code.

Skills

HTML5

CSS / SCSS

- JavaScript
- React.js
- Ruby on Rails
- SQL / MySQL
- Java 8 / Spring
- Jest / TDD

Software Engineering Project

Tic Tac Toe: A Tic-Tac-Toe game made using HTML5, CSS, JavaScript and a Firestore Database Link: https://peglione.github.io/Project-0-Tic-Tac-Toe-Game/public/

Google Books API Search Engine: A search engine for the Google Books API built using SCSS and React.js Link: https://clever-flan-279eab.netlify.app/

React E-Shop: A mock e-commerce app for retro videogames built using React.js and a Firestore Database Link: https://radiant-centaur-30b2cf.netlify.app/

Work History

Software Engineering Trainee at _nology

August 2023 - February 2024

- Learning Unix commands and Git Version Control
- Learning HTML, CSS / SCSS, JavaScript and React.js
- Learning Java, Spring and SQL

Junior Software Engineer at Livewire Markets

May 2021 - March 2023

- Cooperating with UX designers to provide an improved user experience
- Improving website performance by converting it to a higher performing tech stack
- Writing tests and testing changes in a staging environment to enable CD / CI

Education

Software Engineering Immersive at General Assembly, Melbourne

December 2020 - March 2021

A full-time bootcamp teaching front-end and back-end web development.

Bachelor of Art / Bachelor of Science at Monash University, Clayton

March 2013 - June 2017

Majors: Chemistry, Spanish and Latin American Studies

Minors: Earth Sciences, Psychology